Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - M-O
        - M - New York, London, Paris, Munich, 1979; SR-25575; M (Box 49)
          Catalog # SRK 6084; A-side Matrix # SRK-1-6084 S4
          Sire
          Burbank, California
        - Mac, Paul - Seaside electronics EP, 1997; SR-25576; Mac, Paul (Box 49)
          Catalog # FMD 005; A-side Matrix # FMD 005-A1
          Fragmented Records
          United Kingdom
        - Mac Attack - The art of drums, 1986; SR-25577; Mac Attack (Box 49)
          Catalog # 12 HIP-NO 1; A-side Matrix # 12 HIPNO 1
          Baad! Records
        - Machel - Charge (disc one), 1998; SR-25578; Machel; Xtatik (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25579. Double album.
          Catalog # JW145LP; A-side Matrix # JW-145-CHARGE ONE-OLE-1
          JW Productions
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Machel - Charge (disc two), 1998; SR-25579; Machel; Xtatik (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25578. Double album.
          Catalog # JW145LP; A-side Matrix # JW-145-CHARGE TOO-OLE-1
        - Machine - There but for the grace of god go I, 1979; SR-25580; Machine (Box 49)
          Catalog # JD-11484; A-side Matrix # JD-11484 A-1
          RCA
          New York, New York
        - Machine - There but for the grace of god go I, 1979; SR-25581; Machine (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25582. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JD-11484; A-side Matrix # JD-11484-A-1
        - Machine - There but for the grace of god go I (short version), 1979; SR-25582; Machine (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25581. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JD-11457; A-side Matrix # JD-11457-A-1
        - Mack, Jimmie - Jimmie Mack, 1978; SR-25583; Mack, Jimmie (Box 49)
          Catalog # BT 76007; A-side Matrix # ST-BT-784017-B
          Big Tree Records
        - Mack, JJ - You can make it dancin', 1979; SR-25584; Mack, JJ (Box 49)
          Catalog # SA 8525; A-side Matrix # SA 8525 A
          Salsoul Records
        - Mad Doctor X - Picnic with the greys (disc one), 1997; SR-25585; Mad Doctor X (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25586. Double album.
          Catalog # FNTLP2; A-side Matrix # FNTLP-2-A
          Freskanova
          Berks, United Kingdom
        - Mad Doctor X - Picnic with the greys (disc two), 1997; SR-25586; Mad Doctor X (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25585. Double album.
          Catalog # FNTLP2; A-side Matrix # FNTLP-2-C1
        - Madame X - Madame X, 1987; SR-25587; Madame X (Box 49)
          Catalog # 81774-1; A-side Matrix # STA-876461-A
          Atlantic
        - Madhouse - 13, 1987; SR-25588; Madhouse (Box 49)
          Catalog # 0-20893; A-side Matrix # B-30724-SH1-DMM
          Paisley Park
        - Madhouse - 16 (new directions in garage music), 1987; SR-25589; Madhouse (Box 49)
          Catalog # 1-25658; A-side Matrix # 1-25658-A-SR1
        - Madhouse - 8, 1987; SR-25590; Madhouse (Box 49)
          Catalog # 925 545-1; A-side Matrix # 1-25545-A-SH2
        - Madonna - Burning up; Physical attraction, 1983; SR-25591; Madonna (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25592. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-29715; A-side Matrix # B-17806-SH1
        - Madonna - Burning up; Physical attraction, 1983; SR-25592; Madonna (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25591. 2 copies.
        - Madonna - Like a prayer, 1989; SR-25593; Madonna (Box 49)
          Catalog # 1-25844; A-side Matrix # 1-25844-A-SR2-DMM
        - Madonna - Like a virgin, 1984; SR-25594; Madonna (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25595. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1-25157; A-side Matrix # 1-25157-A-RE-1-SH2
        - Madonna - Like a virgin, 1984; SR-25595; Madonna (Box 49)
          In same jacket as # SR-25594. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1-25157; A-side Matrix # 1-25157-A-RE-1-SH5
        - Maelen, Jimmy - Beats workin', 1980; SR-25596; Maelen, Jimmy (Box 49)
          Catalog # AL 36319; A-side Matrix # PAL-36319-1B
          Pavillion
        - Magazine - The correct use of soap, 1980; SR-25597; Magazine (Box 49)
          Catalog # V2156; A-side Matrix # V-2156-A4
          Virgin
          London, United Kingdom
        - Magazine - The correct use of soap, 1980; SR-25598; Magazine (Box 49)
        - Magic Lady - Hot 'n' sassy, 1982; SR-25599; Magic Lady (Box 49)
          Catalog # SP-6-4891; A-side Matrix # A&M SP-06-4891A-G01
          A&M Records
          Santa Monica, California
        - Mahavishnu Orchestra - Birds of fire, 1973; SR-25600; Mahavishnu Orchestra (Box 50)
          Catalog # AL 31996; A-side Matrix # P AL-31996-2A
          Columbia
        - Mahlathini & Mahotella Queens - Paris-soweto, 1988; SR-25601; Mahlathini & Mahotella Queens (Box 50)
          Catalog # 66829-1; A-side Matrix # 66829-1 A
          Celluloid
          Paris, France
        - Mahlathini & Mahotella Queens - Kazet, 1988; SR-25602; Mahlathini & Mahotella Queens (Box 50)
          Catalog # 66829-6; A-side Matrix # 66829-6 A
        - Mahoaney, Skip - Land of love, 1976; SR-25603; Mahoaney, Skip; Casuals (Box 50)
          Catalog # ABET 410; A-side Matrix # ABET-410-A
          Abet
          Nashville, Tennessee
        - Mahogany - Bye bye, 2001; SR-25604; Mahogany (Box 50)
          Catalog # WTEN004; A-side Matrix # WTEN 004 A1
          W10
        - Maia, Tim - Tim Maia, 1986; SR-25605; Maia, Tim (Box 50)
          Catalog # 2451 041; A-side Matrix # 2451 041
          Polydor
          Brazil
        - Main Ingredient - Party people, 1981; SR-25606; Main Ingredient; Gooding, Cuba (Box 50)
          Catalog # JD-13046; A-side Matrix # PD-13046-A-1
        - Makaga, Didier - Didier Makaga, 1984; SR-25607; Makaga, Didier (Box 50)
          Catalog # 24 0346-1; A-side Matrix # WEA 24 03 46-1 A
          WEA
          France
        - Makaga, Didier - Jamais deux sans toi, 1983; SR-25608; Makaga, Didier (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25609. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 24 0069-1; A-side Matrix # WEA 240069-1 A1
        - Makaga, Didier - Jamais deux sans toi, 1983; SR-25609; Makaga, Didier (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25608. 2 copies.
        - Malemen - Express male, 1984; SR-25610; Malemen (Box 50)
          Catalog # 422-814 983-1 M-1; A-side Matrix # 42-814 983-1-AS-PRC-C 1-1-1
          Mercury
        - Malibu - Goin cruisin, 1983; SR-25611; Malibu (Box 50)
          Catalog # BOB 27; A-side Matrix # BOB-27-SIDE LA BY DAY
          Bobcat Records
        - Mammatapee - On the one, 1980; SR-25612; Mammatapee (Box 50)
          Catalog # WHK 3510; A-side Matrix # WHK-1-3510 LW2
          Whitfield Records
        - Mandrell, Barbara - The best of Barbara Mandrell, 1979; SR-25613; Mandrell, Barbara (Box 50)
          Catalog # AY-1119; A-side Matrix # AY-1119-A
          ABC Records
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Mandrell, Barbara - Moods, 1978; SR-25614; Mandrell, Barbara (Box 50)
          Catalog # AY-1088; A-side Matrix # AY-1088-A-1
        - Mandrill - Mandrilland (disc one), 1974; SR-25615; Mandrill (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25616. Double album.
          Catalog # PD-2-9002; A-side Matrix # PD2-9002-A-4
        - Mandrill - Mandrilland (disc two), 1974; SR-25616; Mandrill (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25615. Double album.
          Catalog # PD-2-9002; A-side Matrix # PD2-9002-C-4
        - Mandrill - Mandrill is, 1972; SR-25617; Mandrill (Box 50)
          Catalog # PD-5025; A-side Matrix # POLP-80271-1B
        - Mandrill - Having a love attack; Don't stop; Stay tonite, 1978; SR-25618; Mandrill (Box 50)
          Catalog # SP-44; A-side Matrix # SP 44 SA
          Arista
        - Mane, Kaba - Chefo mae mae, 1986; SR-25619; Mane, Kaba (Box 50)
          Catalog # ESP 7519; A-side Matrix # ESP 7519-A
          Disques Esperance
        - Manfat 4 - Excessive groove, 1999; SR-25620; Manfat 4 (Box 50)
          Catalog # RKDK 007; A-side Matrix # RKDK 007-AA1
          Rinkydink Records
        - Mafila, Kanté - Musicale Mandingue, 1985; SR-25621; Mafila, Kanté (Box 50)
          Catalog # TAN 7016; A-side Matrix # TAN 7016A
          Tangent
        - Manfred Mann's Earth Band - Somewhere in Afrika, 1982; SR-25622; Manfred Mann's Earth Band (Box 50)
          Catalog # 205 077; A-side Matrix # 205077 A-2
          Bronze
        - Manhattan Transfer - Extensions, 1979; SR-25623; Manhattan Transfer (Box 50)
          Catalog # ST-A-794389-SP; A-side Matrix # STA-794389-B
        - Manhattans - After midnight, 1980; SR-25624; Manhattans (Box 50)
          Catalog # AL 36411; A-side Matrix # P AL- 36411-1AE
        - Manilow, Barry - Copacabana (at the Copa), 1978; SR-25625; Manilow, Barry (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25626. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-18; A-side Matrix # #2591-5-Z
        - Manilow, Barry - Copacabana (at the Copa), 1978; SR-25626; Manilow, Barry (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25625. 2 copies.
        - Manolo - Manolo, 1979; SR-25627; Manolo (Box 50)
          Catalog # SP-4783; A-side Matrix # AMSP4783A-T2
        - Mann, Herbie - Brazil-once again, 1978; SR-25628; Mann, Herbie (Box 50)
          Catalog # SD 19169; A-side Matrix # ST-A-773909-B
        - Mansulu and his Haitians - Santeria Haitiana por autenticos santeros Haitianos, 1959; SR-25629; Mansulu and his Haitians (Box 50)
          Catalog # H-531; A-side Matrix # HAITI-531-A
          Haiti Records
          Port-au-Prince, Haiti
        - Mantra - Mantra, 1981; SR-25630; Mantra (Box 50)
          Catalog # NBLP 7256; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7256-AS-PW
          Casablanca
          Los Angeles, California
        - Mantronix - In full effect, 1988; SR-25631; Mantronix (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25632. 2 copies.
          Catalog # C1-48336; A-side Matrix # C1-1-48336-Z1
          Capitol Records
          Hollywood, California
        - Mantronix - In full effect, 1988; SR-25632; Mantronix (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25631. 2 copies.
          Catalog # C1-48336; A-side Matrix # C1-1-48336-Z2
        - Mantronix - In full effect, 1988; SR-25633; Mantronix (Box 50)
        - Manuella - Don't try to come back to me, 1993; SR-25634; Manuella (Box 50)
          Catalog # MRC TIA 9002; A-side Matrix # MRC TIA-9002-A
          Ti Amo Records
          Newark, New Jersey
        - Marcé et Toumpak - Zouk chouv', 1987; SR-25635; Marcé et Toumpak (Box 50)
          Catalog # ORB 035; A-side Matrix # DMC-4286 A-1
          Globe Style
        - Marku - Marku, 1973; SR-25636; Marku (Box 50)
          Catalog # CLP-11726; A-side Matrix # MLP-11726-A
          Underground
        - Marley, Bob - Babylon by bus (disc one), 1978; SR-25637; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25638. Double album.
          Catalog # 90029-1-I; A-side Matrix # ST IL 825067-A 1-1
          Island
        - Marley, Bob - Babylon by bus (disc two), 1978; SR-25638; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25637. Double album.
          Catalog # 90029-1-I; A-side Matrix # ST IL 825069-A 1-1
        - Marley, Bob - Babylon by bus (disc one), 1978; SR-25639; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25640. Double album.
          Catalog # ST-IL-825067-SP; A-side Matrix # ST IL 825068-A 1-1
        - Marley, Bob - Babylon by bus (disc two), 1978; SR-25640; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25639. Double album.
          Catalog # ST-IL-825067-SP; A-side Matrix # ST IL 825069-A 1-1
        - Marley, Bob - Exodus, 1977; SR-25641; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 50)
          Catalog # 90034-1; A-side Matrix # ST-IL-825079-A
        - Marley, Bob - The best of Bob Marley & The Wailers, 1976; SR-25642; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 50)
          Catalog # SO 1106; A-side Matrix # SO 1106A-1
          Studio One
        - Marley, Bob - Confrontation, 1983; SR-25643; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 50)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # BMW 9760 A
          Rita Marley Music
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Marley Marl - In control, volume 1, 1988; SR-25644; Marley Marl (Box 50)
          Catalog # 1-25783; A-side Matrix # 1-25783-A-SR2
          Cold Chillin'
        - Marley Marl - The Queensbridge sessions, 1996; SR-25645; Marley Marl (Box 50)
          Catalog # OSF LP 4020; A-side Matrix # OSP-LP-4020-A
          Tuff City
        - Marley, Ziggy - Hey world, 1986; SR-25646; Marley, Ziggy; Melody Makers (Box 50)
          Catalog # ST-17234; A-side Matrix # ST-1-17234-P-2
          EMI America
        - Marley, Ziggy - Look who's dancing, 1989; SR-25647; Marley, Ziggy; Melody Makers (Box 50)
          Catalog # VUST 5; A-side Matrix # VUST 5 A-4U-1-1
          United States
        - Martha and the Vandellas - Greatest hits, 1981; SR-25648; Martha and the Vandellas; Reeves, Martha; Vandellas (Box 50)
          Catalog # M5-204V1; A-side Matrix # M5-204V1-A-08A
          Motown
        - Marthely, Jean-Philippe - Kassav', 1985; SR-25649; Marthely, Jean-Philippe; Saint-Eloi, Patrick (Box 50)
          Catalog # GD 034; A-side Matrix # GD 034 A
          GD Productions
        - Martina - Central park; Let it in, 1981; SR-25650; Martina (Box 50)
          Catalog # BRDS 2515; A-side Matrix # BRDS-2515-A
          Brass Records
        - Martinez, Angie - Dem thangs, 2001; SR-25651; Martinez, Angie (Box 50)
          Catalog # 67182-0; A-side Matrix # STED-67182A-1
          Elektra
        - Mary Jane Girls - Mary Jane Girls, 1983; SR-25652; Mary Jane Girls (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25653. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 6040GLA; A-side Matrix # 6040-GL-A-15A-ZMT
          Gordy
        - Mary Jane Girls - Mary Jane Girls, 1983; SR-25653; Mary Jane Girls (Box 50)
          In same jacket as # SR-25652. 2 copies.
        - Marz - Make it right, 1982; SR-25654; Marz (Box 51)
          Catalog # LT-51122; A-side Matrix # LT-1-51122-Z-2
          Liberty
        - Masekela, Hugh - You told your mama not to worry, 1977; SR-25655; Masekela, Hugh (Box 51)
          Catalog # NBLP 7079; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7079-AS-SM
        - Masekela, Hugh - The promise of a future, 1968; SR-25656; Masekela, Hugh (Box 51)
          Catalog # 73028; A-side Matrix # US-1054-T5
          UNI Records
        - Mason - Pour it on, 1986; SR-25657; Mason (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25658. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ED 5243; A-side Matrix # STED-66795-A-1
        - Mason - Pour it on, 1986; SR-25658; Mason (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25657. 2 copies.
        - Mason - Double-x-posure, 1986; SR-25659; Mason (Box 51)
          Catalog # ED 5198; A-side Matrix # STED-5198-A-1
        - Mason, Barbara - I am your woman, she is your wife, 1978; SR-25660; Mason, Barbara (Box 51)
          Catalog # PRL 12159; A-side Matrix # PRL-12159AS
          Prelude Records
        - Mason, Harvey - M.V.P., 1981; SR-25661; Mason, Harvey (Box 51)
          Catalog # AB 4283; A-side Matrix # AB4283-SA-1A
        - Mason, Vaughan - Roller skate; Cravin your body, 1980; SR-25662; Mason, Vaughan; Crew; Vaughan Mason & Crew (Box 51)
          Catalog # D 212; A-side Matrix # 7-1021-1B
          Brunswick
          Chapel Hill, North Carolina
        - Mass Production - Turn up the music, 1981; SR-25663; Mass Production (Box 51)
          Catalog # SD 5226; A-side Matrix # ST-ON-814663-C
          Cotillion
        - Mass Production - Believe, 1977; SR-25664; Mass Production (Box 51)
          Catalog # SD 9918; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-773903-B
        - Mass Production - Massterpiece, 1980; SR-25665; Mass Production (Box 51)
          Catalog # SD 5218; A-side Matrix # STCTN-804439-A
        - Mass Production - Groove me; Slow bump, 1978; SR-25666; Mass Production (Box 51)
          Catalog # DSKO 140; A-side Matrix # ST-DK-36109-1
        - Mass Production - Love you, 1979; SR-25667; Mass Production (Box 51)
          Catalog # DSKO 210; A-side Matrix # STDK 37134-1
        - Mass Production - In the purest form, 1979; SR-25087; Mass Production (Box 51)
          Catalog # SD 5211; A-side Matrix # ST CTN-794233-A
        - Massive Attack - Blue lines, 1980; SR-25668; Massive Attack (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25669. 2 copies.
          Catalog # WBRLP 1; A-side Matrix # WBRLP 1 A-02-01
          Wild Bunch Records
        - Massive Attack - Blue lines, 1980; SR-25669; Massive Attack (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25668. 2 copies.
        - Master Freez - Amen; Get up on your feet, 1991; SR-25670; Master Freez (Box 51)
          Catalog # OZ 013; A-side Matrix # OZ-013-A
          Onizom Music
          Bologna, Italy
        - Master P - Da ballers, 1999; SR-25671; Master P (Box 51)
          Catalog # SPRO 81298; A-side Matrix # 08724-81298-1-A
          No Limit Records
        - Masterfleet - High on the sea, 1974; SR-25672; Masterfleet (Box 51)
          Catalog # SRA 8028; A-side Matrix # SRA 8028 RE1A
          Sussex
        - Masterpiece - The girl's alright with me, 1980; SR-25673; Masterpiece (Box 51)
          Catalog # WHK 3389; A-side Matrix # WHK-1-3389-CW3
        - Masters of Ceremony - Redder pose, 1988; SR-25674; Masters of Ceremony (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25675. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BWAY 473; A-side Matrix # BWAY-473-A
          4th and Broadway
        - Masters of Ceremony - Redder pose, 1988; SR-25675; Masters of Ceremony (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25674. 2 copies.
        - Material - I'm the one, 1982; SR-25676; Material (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25677. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-67970; A-side Matrix # 0-67970-THAT SIDE-2-SP
        - Material - I'm the one, 1982; SR-25677; Material (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25676. 2 copies.
        - Material - For a few dollars more, 1984; SR-25678; Material (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25679. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 8327; A-side Matrix # 8327-A
          Carrere
        - Material - For a few dollars more, 1984; SR-25679; Material (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25678. 2 copies.
        - Material - One down, 1982; SR-25680; Material (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25681. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 60206; A-side Matrix # 60206-A-1-RE-SP
        - Material - One down, 1982; SR-25681; Material (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25680. 2 copies.
        - Mathematiques Modernes - Les visiteurs du soir, 1981; SR-25682; Mathematiques Modernes (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25683. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 529802; A-side Matrix # YPARTX 88532 1
          Dorian
        - Mathematiques Modernes - Les visiteurs du soir, 1981; SR-25683; Mathematiques Modernes (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25682. 2 copies.
        - Mathis, Kathy - Katt walk, 1987; SR-25684; Mathis, Kathy (Box 51)
          Catalog # FZ 40539; A-side Matrix # PAL-40539-1A
          Tabu Records
        - Matt & La Brigade - J'croyais en toi, 2000; SR-25685; Matt & La Brigade (Box 51)
          Catalog # 561796-1; A-side Matrix # 561796-1A
          Universal Records
        - Maupin, Bennie - Moonscapes, 1978; SR-25686; Maupin, Bennie (Box 51)
          Catalog # SRM-1-3717; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-3717-CT-A2
        - Maurice - This is acid (a new dance craze), 1988; SR-25688; Maurice; Joshua, Maurice (Box 51)
          Catalog # VE-7016; A-side Matrix # A+M-VE-07016-AA-SP1
          Vendetta Records
        - Maxayn - Bail out for fun!, 1974; SR-25689; Maxayn (Box 51)
          Catalog # CP 0125; A-side Matrix # CP0125 40727 RE1
          Capricorn Records
        - Maxwell - Now, 2001; SR-25690; Maxwell (Box 51)
          Catalog # C 67136; A-side Matrix # AL-67136-1B
        - Mayday - Mayday, 1981; SR-25691; Mayday (Box 51)
          Catalog # SP-4873; A-side Matrix # A+M-SP-04873-A-T1